A Southern Whip-Ass Extravaganza!
The Baytown Outlaws is a action, comedy, crime film directed by Barry Battles.
When three redneck brothers agree to help a woman save her son from an abusive
father, they become targets on the run from an odd cast of characters.
Brick Oodie, played by Clayne Crawford.
McQueen Oodie, played by Travis Fimmel.
Lincoln Oodie, played by Daniel Cudmore.
Rob, played by Thomas Brodie-Sangster.
Millard, played by Andre Braugher.
Reese, played by Paul Wesley.
The Baytown Outlaws is a 2012 action comedy film directed by Barry Battles in
his directorial debut, and written by Battles and Griffin Hood.
The film stars Andre Braugher, Clayne Crawford, Daniel Cudmore, Travis
Fimmel, Eva Longoria, Paul Wesley, and Billy Bob Thornton.
The film follows the Oodie brothers -
Brick, Lincoln, and McQueen -
who act as vigilante killers for the local sheriff.
When the trio accepts a job to rescue a young boy from his godfather, plans quickly fall apart as
the brothers aim to deliver the boy to safety while pursued by groups of assassins.
The film explores themes of fight, gas station, anti hero, murder, mute.
The tone is lighthearted.